[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What geographical area does the Diamond Dove populate?", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["Europe", "Asia", "South America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not one of the colloquial nicknames of the pieces of the domino set?", "correct_answer": "They all are", "incorrect_answers": ["Stones", "Spinners", "Bones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fill in the missing words said by the Phantom in the movie The Phantom of the Opera:\nLook at your _______ in the ___________! I am there inside!", "correct_answer": "face; mirror", "incorrect_answers": ["face; Phantom", "eyes; mirror", "head; sunshine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You can get lead poisoning from a modern pencil.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the gin rummy game which of the following is a triangle?", "correct_answer": "7 of hearts, 8 of hearts, 7 of spades", "incorrect_answers": ["7 of hearts, 8 of clubs, 7 of spades", "7 of hearts, 8 of hearts, 6 of hearts", "7 of hearts, 8 of clubs, 8 of diamonds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A woman in the final stage of her pregnancy should not wear under-wired bras.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the tagline for the 1987 movie Wall Street directed by Oliver Stone?", "correct_answer": "Every dream has a price.", "incorrect_answers": ["Poor is the man who does not realize what he possesses.", "You can never be too wealthy.", "The more you get, the more you want."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are Lacoste boutiques in Europe.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Greek mythological figure flew too close to the sun with his wings made of wax?", "correct_answer": "Icarus", "incorrect_answers": ["Pasiphae", "Ariadne", "Daedalus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bamako is the capital of Madagascar.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Die Hard, throughout his ordeal in the building, McClane stays in radio contact with which LAPD Sgt.?", "correct_answer": "Al Powell", "incorrect_answers": ["Kevin Hames", "Stuart Simons", "Po Loi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meal is the godro-godro, which is very popular in the Madagascar cuisine?", "correct_answer": "Pudding", "incorrect_answers": ["Seafood meal", "Rice meal", "Vegetable stew"]}]